Cristhian Cano

Systems Engineer

• Armenia quindio in cristhian cano • criscano11

★ cristhian-cano.com



Profile

Systems engineer with experience in software development, gathering requirements, design, installation, testing and maintenance. Mastery of several languages and systems. Able to self-manage and be effective in independent projects. Good collaboration skills within a productive team.

Professional Experience

Cerok, Web Developer ⊘

Provide solutions to scheduled requirements effectively. document the requirements carried out according to the company's guidelines, comply in quality and time with the requirements according to the assigned schedule, orderly, teamwork, reliability, effective communication, commitment, information processing, effective communication with related areas of the company, verify and understand the analysis and design, in addition to the field matrix and use cases to parameterize the new client modules, perform unit tests of the new modules before passing it to the support and quality area for review . carry out maintenance manual of the developed processes. record the progress in each ticket developed of the base software used, handling technologies such as PHP, Symfony, Iquery, Bootstrap,

04/2023 – present Remote, Pereira/Rda

Knowledge System, Web Developer ⊘

Improve current software, evaluate the quality of the developments carried out, document the code under the protocols defined by the technology development and infrastructure area. Deliver reports on project progress, develop new code to update, improve or create new solutions according to defined work plans. using technologies such as React.js \cdot MongoDB \cdot Docker \cdot Ruby \cdot Ruby on Rails \cdot Bootstrap \cdot Ubuntu \cdot MySQL \cdot JavaScript

06/2022 – present Remote, Bogotá

Freelance, Web Developer

As a freelance Web Developer, I am responsible for creating and maintaining high-performance web applications and exceptional user experiences. responsible for the implementation of designs and functionalities that improve user interaction with our online platforms. performing requirements gathering, design, installation, testing and maintenance with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Codeigniter, MySQL, Bootstrap, PHP, Ruby on Rails

01/2021 – present Remote, Armenia

Languages

English(A2) • Spanish(Native)

Education

02/2022 – 05/2022 Bogota Colombia

Santa Rosa de Cabal University Corporation - UNISARC,

Systems Engineer

01/2018 – 04/2022 Saint Rose of Cabal, Risaralda

Skills

- ReacJS

- MongoDB

- PHP

- JavaScript

- Bootstrap

- MySQL

- Ruby on Rails

- JQuery

- Docker